Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
- Series XXII. Farmworker Related Organizations
  - Farmworker Rights Organization, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Western New York Rural Legal Services, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Farmworker Legal Services, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Migrant Legal Action (National), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Rural America, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Genesco Migrant Program / Gloria Mattera Returns to Teaching (1979), Death (1988) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Interagency Coordinating Committee on Migrant and Rural Poor, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - National Association of Farmworker Organizations, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Interagency Coordinating Committee (New York State), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Interagency Coordinating Committee on Migrant and Rural Poor, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Organizations in New York State, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - National Migrant Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - East Coast Migrant Head Start, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - New York State Department of Labor, 1985-2000 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Agri-Business Child Development (ABCD) History (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Agri-Business Child Development (ABCD), 1987-2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Ag. and Markets Child Care Program (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Minimum Wage Advisory Council (New York State), 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Interagency Coordinating Committee on Farmworkers (New York State), 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Interagency Coordinating Committee on Farmworkers (New York State), 1992-94 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Coalition for Social and Economic Justice (New York State), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Office of Rural Affairs (New York State), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Farmworker Legal Services of New York, 1992-2004 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Labor Laws in New York State: Unequal and Unjust Treatment for Farmworkers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Migrant and Rural Ministry - Niagara County, New York, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Rural Law Center (New York State), 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Farmworker Law Project (New York State), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - CITA (Independent Farmworkers' Center) New York State, 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Organization for Labor Action (COLA) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - PCUN (Northwest Treeplanters and Farmworkers United), 2000 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Labor-Religion Coalition (New York State) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - USA Farmworker PAC, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Incident Reports - Working Together, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Student Action with Farmworkers (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Sowing Seeds for Justice Dinner, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Series XXIII. Videos
  - Harvest of Shame - Edward R. Murrow, no date; 1; VHS (Box 25)
  - Farmworkers and Pesticides, Kate Wolfe Series ABC, no date; 2; VHS (Box 25)
  - Migrant Farmworkers - "The Work", no date; 3; VHS (Box 25)
  - Migrant Farmworkers in Wayne County (New York State) Cornell Students, 1990; 4; VHS (Box 25)
  - New Harvest - Old Shame - Frontline, 1990; 5; VHS (Box 25)
  - South Carolina Creek, H-2 Workers, Jamaicans in Florida, 1991; 6; VHS (Box 25)
  - The Liberators (The American Experience), no date; 7; VHS (Box 25)
  - Orange Pickers In Florida, King Ferry Camp, Liberators, American Experience, no date; 8; VHS (Box 25)
  - Legacy of Shame- 60 Minutes, 1995; 9; VHS (Box 25)
  - Child Labor in the Fields - Dateline, 1998; 10; VHS (Box 25)
  - Where's the Beef? - 60 Minutes, 1999; 11; VHS (Box 25)
  - The Voice of the Farmer - 60 Minutes, 2000; 12; VHS (Box 25)
  - Coming Up on the Season, Cornell Migrant Program, 2001; 13; VHS (Box 25)
  - Aumento ya! (A Raise Now!), PCUN, 1996; 14; VHS (Box 25)
  - BME: Migrant Education in New York State, 1980; 1; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Brockport Migrant Education Project: A Migrant Experience and Las Aspiraciones de una Hija, no date; 2; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Fredonia Migrant Tutorial Pilot: "Reaching Out" (dub), no date; 3; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Goals for Youth (dub), no date; 4; U-matic (Box 51)
  - WOKR-TV 13 (Rochester, NY): series on migrant workers, 1981; 5; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Fields of Dignity (The Migrant Farmer Worker), 1982-09-16; 6; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Brockport (no other title), no date; 7; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Goals for Youth, no date; 8; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Brockport Migrant Education Project: Constancia's Choice, 1986-09; 9; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Brockport Migrant Education Project: Reflections of 15 Years and Fields of Dignity, no date; 10; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Apple Picking, 1983-09-23; 11; U-matic (Box 51)
  - A Migrant Experience, no date; 12; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Keith Moody segment of "PM Magazine", no date; 13; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Players #1 (no other title), no date; 14; U-matic (Box 51)
  - Mexican Farm Workers: "Harvest to Harvard", no date; 15; U-matic (Box 51)
  - I Still Can't Say It: Documentary about preventing child abuse (Cornell University), 1987-06-16; 16; VHS (Box 51)
  - Brockport Migrant Education Project: "Reflections of 15 Years" (Texas Interstate Program), 1981; 17; VHS (Box 51)
- Series XXIV. Posters, drawings, misc.
  - Posters for exhibit at the DeWitt Historical Society of Tompkins County-, 2002-02 (Box 50)
  - Tin sign for the Cornell Migrant Program (Box 50)
  - painting of DeMay Camp by Joyce Metz, 1967 (Box 50)
  - Comic book drawings used for pesticide education packet, 1983 (Box 50)